const PyLanguage =[
    {
        question: "Who developed Python Programming Language?",

        ans: 3,

        option:[
            "A)Wick van Rossum",
            "B)Rasmus Lerdorf",
            "c) Guido van Rossum",
            "d) Niene Stom"

        ],
    },


{
    question: "Which of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",

    ans: 3,

    option:[
        "a) .python",
        "b) .pl",
        "c) .py",
        "d) .p",
    ],
},


{
    question: "Which type of Programming does Python support?",

    ans: 4,

    option:[
        "a)  object-oriented programming",
        "b) structured programming",
        "c) functional programming",
        "d) all of the mentioned",
    ],
},


{
    question: "Which of the following statements is used to create an empty set in Python?",

    ans: 4,

    option:[
        "a)  ()",
        "b) []",
        "c) {}",
        "d) set()",
    ],
},


{
    question: "Which of the following character is used to give single-line comments in Python?",

    ans: 2,

    option:[
        "a)  //",
        "b) #",
        "c) !",
        "d) /*",
    ],
},

{
    question: "Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?",

    ans: "A",

    option:[
        "a) Identation",
        "b) Key",
        "c) Brackets",
        "d) All of the mentioned",
    ],
},


{
    question: "Which of the following functions is a built-in function in python?",

    ans: 2,

    option:[
        "a) factorial()",
        "b) print()",
        "c) speed()",
        "d) sqrt()",
    ],
},


{
    question: "What will be the output of the following Python function?",

    ans: 2,

    option:[
        "a) pass",
        "b)eval",
        "c) assert",
        "d) nonlocal",
    ],
},


{
    question: "What does pip stand for python?",

    ans: 3,

    option:[
        "a) Pip installs python",
        "b) pip installs package",
        "c) preferred installer program",
        "d) all of the mention",
    ],
},


{
    question: "Which of the following functions can help us to find the version of python that we are currently working on?",

    ans: 4,
   
    option:[
        "a) sys.version(1)",
        "b) sys.version(0)",
        "c) sys.version(2)",
        "d) sys.version",
    ],
},
];